I can't keep up.
Let us pray. Almighty God, our Heavenly Father, send down upon these who hold office in this
city the spirit of wisdom, charity, and justice, that with steadfast purpose they
may faithfully serve in their offices to promote the well-being of all people, through Jesus Christ our Lord. Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America, and to the republic for which it stands, one nation under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
Claims.
Six minutes from the September 5th, 2023 River meeting.
Seven. Fidel Stratton, Edmunds and Palmer claim for jury re-licensing the amount of $1,500.
So Mayor, members of the council, in your packet you should have an invoice for $1,500 to Fidel Stratton.
This was before professional services incurred July 24th, 2023 to August 16th, 2023, most of which that time was spent reviewing and commenting on responses that were developed for the city on behalf of the city to perk,
and also reviewing and including tribal comments and legal decisions.
Eight. Tetra Tech claim for the Osha River 2D modeling in the amount of $14,166.
So Mayor, members of the council, again, you have an invoice in your packet of $14,166.
And again, this is our continuation of the Osha River 2D modeling from May 24th, 2023 to August 18th, 2023, including the development and pre-gan sanitation transport model that we've been working so much on.
Again, we have a current amount given the previous approval of Fidel Stratton that would leave us $711,183.85 budget for these items.
If the $14,166 approved, that would leave us this fiscal year $697,17.85.
Motion approved.
Second.
Total.
Williams.
Sunberg.
Harper.
Aye.
Nine, budget amendment 24-2 adjustments to the estimated MSU Bay carryover, actual carryover, and re-numbering of funds.
This special amendment, you'll see one on the next meeting also, is to allow different departments, actually this is for two different funds for the MSU Bay and the school mortar fund.
It is monies that were budgeted last year.
They did not, they were not able to spend it either because they couldn't get it in time, but in the year.
This is allowing them input.
Those monies were not included in the carryover, so we feel comfortable allowing them to increase the carryover to spend it this year.
Ten.
I will be in business if any of us are in business at the closing of this agenda.
Eleven.
Staff report.
Twelve.
Trustee, community announcements.
Four.
Dean, adjournment.
Total.
Williams.
Sunberg.
Harper.
Aye.